Guide to the Bob Holman Audio/Video Poetry Collection 1977-2002 MSS 128
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XI: Miscellaneous Video and Film, ca. 1995-1999
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - R. Gaines: "CAB", Undated (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0779)
    - SLAM: Bob Holman, Undated (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0780)
    - Washington Square Films - Compilation Reel: Tape 5 of 7, 1993 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0781)
    - Matt Cook, Undated (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0782)
    - J: We Are The Majority, 1992 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0783)
    - J.: "Keep the Promise", 1993 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0784)
    - Eiléan Ni Chuilleanain & Nuala Ni Dhomhnaill, 1997 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0785)
    - Yehuda Amichai, 1989 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0786)
    - Robert Creeley, 1990 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0787)
    - NVI Edit Black, 1991 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0788)
    - [Unknown], Undated (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0789)
    - New York In Verse, 1995 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0790)
    - nycSLAMS, 2000 (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0791)
    - Bob Holman: Pass 2, Undated (Box 32, Media ID: 128.0792)
    - Postmodern Pobre, 1992 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0793)
    - Giovanni, Pound, Whitman, Williams, Undated (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0794)
    - George D. Kovach: Kean College Forum, Undated (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0795)
    - Sekou Sundiata: "Language of Life", Undated (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0796)
    - Sekou Sundiata, Undated (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0797)
    - Maggie Estep: "No More Mister Nice Guy" - CD Master Tape, 1994 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0798A)
    - Maggie Estep: "No More Mister Nice Guy" - 1997 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0799A)
    - Maggie Estep/ Poetry: Showbiz Today (CNN), 1994 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0800)
    - Maggie Estep/ Poetry: Showbiz Today (CNN), 1994 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0801)
    - Alterna Vision Vol. 42, Undated (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0802A)
    - Maggie Estep: R&R With Roger Rose, 1994 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0803)
    - Hal Sirowitz: MTV's Spoken Word Unplugged April 1995 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0804)
    - Allen Ginsberg on CNN Live & Larry King Live, 1996 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0805)
    - Allen Ginsberg on New York 1 & MTV News, 1996 (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0806)
    - Slammin' (Trailer), Undated (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0807)
    - Slammin', Undated (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0808)
    - Haiku, Undated (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0809)
      Format: 16 mm. Film
    - Poetry For Me!, Undated (Box 33, Media ID: 128.0810)
- Series XII: Vinyl Sound Recordings
  - Subseries A: Vinyl Recordings - LPs, 12 in.
    - Sebastian Cabot, Actor, A Dramatic Reading With Music, Bob Dylan, Poet; MGM Records (Box 34)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
    - Greatest Rap Hits Volume 2; Sugar Hill Records (Box 34)
    - Boogie Down Productions, By All Means Necessary; Zomba Production Ltd. (Box 34)
    - You're the Guy I Want to Share My Money With, Laurie Anderson, John Giorno, William S. Burroughs; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - Sugar, Alcohol, and Meat, The Dial-a-Poem Poets; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - Sugar, Alcohol, and Meat, The Dial-a-Poem Poets; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - The Dial-a-Poem Poets; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - Big Ego, The Dial-a-Poem Poets; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - John Giorno and Anne Waldman; Giorno Poetry Systems Records (Box 34)
    - Yale Series of Recorded Poets, Louis MacNeice Reads From His Own Works; Decca Records (Box 34)
    - The Poetry of George Sefris Read in Greek by the Author and in English by the Translator Edmund Keeley; Caedmon Records (Box 34)
    - The Firesign Theatre Presents The Tale of the Giant Rat of Sumatra; Columbia Records (Box 34)
    - Master Arts Series Allan Hodshire Presents Burke McHugh's Greenwich Village, USA, Unexpurgated Complete Edition; 20th Fox Record Corporation (Box 34)
    - Philadelphia International Records, Jocko; CBS Records (Box 34)
    - Joeski Love, Pee-wee's Dance; Vintertainment (Box 34)
    - Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew, Oh, My God!; Danya Records, Ltd. (Box 34)
    - UTFO, Full Force; Select Records (Box 34)
    - Sweet Soul Music; Enjoy Records (Box 34)
    - Ras Tefsa; Jafrica Records (Box 34)
    - Do You Like That Funky Beat (Ahh Beat, Beat) Kyle Brinson, Kool Kyle the Starchild and the Disco Dolls, Ronnie Ron and Crew; Enjoy Records (Box 34)
    - Congo; Nine Nine Records (Box 34)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, 45 rpm; 12 in.
    - Boogie Down Productions, Ghetto Music: The Blueprint of Hip Hop; Zomba Recording Corp. (Box 34)
    - Run-D.M.C, King of Rock; Profile Records, Inc. (Box 34)
    - L.L. Cool J, I Can Give You More/I Can't Live Without My Radio; Def Jam Recordings (Box 34)
    - L.L. Cool J, I Need a Beat/You'll Rock (Remix); Def Jam Recordings (Box 34)
    - Triple Threat by Z-3 MCs; Beauty and the Beat Records (Box 34)
    - Cameo Word Up; Polygram Records (Box 34)
    - Party Time, Dimples D.; Streetwise Records (Box 34)
    - Run-D.M.C.; Profile Records, Inc. (Box 34)
    - Roxanne (with UTFO); Select Records (Box 34)
    - Roxanne Shante; Pop Art Records (Box 34)
    - Malcolm X: Music by Keith LeBlanc; Tommy Boy Music (Box 34)
    - Afrika Bambaataa and the Jazzy 5/ The Kryptic Krew featuring Tina B: Jazzy Sensation; Tommy Boy Music (Box 34)
    - Greatest Beats; Tommy Boy Music (Box 34)
    - Afrika Bambaata and the Soul Sonic Force: Planet Rock; Tommy Boy Music (Box 34)
    - The Firesign Theatre: Don't Crush That Dwarf, Hand me the Pliers; Columbia Records (Box 34)
    - Proctor and Bergman: TV or Not TV; Columbia Records (Box 34)
    - Firesign Theatre Sez Everything You Know is Wrong; Columbia Records (Box 34)
    - The Black Flames/ b/w The Public Enemy: from the original Soundtrack of the Tewntieth Century Fox Film Less Than Zero; Def Jam Recordings (Box 34)
    - LL Cool J, I Need a Beat; Def Jam Recordings (Box 35)
    - Sun City, Artists United Against Apartheid; Manhattan Records (Box 35)
    - LL Cool J, Rock the Bells; Def Jam Recordings (Box 35)
    - Shinehead: Chain Gang-Rap; Elektra/ Asylum Records (Box 35)
    - Fast Money; Star Maker Records (Box 35)
    - Disco 45: Rapper's Delight; Joe Gibbs Music Corp. (Box 35)
    - Firesign Theatre Predicts in the Next World You're on Your Own; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre: "Fighting Clowns;" Rhino Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre Presents Waiting for the Electrician or Someone Like Him; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre Lawyer's Hospital; Rhino Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Comedy of Proctor and Bergman: Give Us a Break; Mercury (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre: I Think We're All Bozos on This Bus; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - David Ossman's How Time Flys: A Hi-Fi Sci-Fi Comedy Starring The Firesign Theatre; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - Roxanne (Fly) Shante Featuring Steady "B": I'm Fly Shante; Pop Art Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre: Not Insane; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre Presents Nick Danger, Third Eye: The Case of the Missing Shoe; Rhino Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Firesign Theatre Presents "Fighting Clowns," With Special Limited Edition 7" Picture Disc; Rhino Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - Spike Jones, The Craziest Show on Earth; M.F. Distribution Co., Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Conception Corporation Presents Conceptionland and Other States of Mind; Cotillion (Box 35)
    - Bob Newhart, The Button-Down Man Strikes Back!; Warner Bros. Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - The Best of Stan Fredberg; Capitol Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - National Lampoon Radio Dinner; Banana Records (Box 35)
    - The Marx Bros.: The Original Voice Tracks from Their Greatest Movies; Decca Records (Box 35)
    - William E. McEuen Presents Steve Martin: "Let's Get Small;" Warner Bros. Records, Inc. (Box 35)
    - Movies are Better Than Ever, Jonathan Winters; Verve Records (Box 35)
    - W.C. Fields and Mae West; Proscenium Records (Box 35)
    - Dear Friends: The Firesign Theatre; Columbia Records (Box 35)
    - An Anthology of French Poetry Volume Two: From Pierre Corneille to Charles Baudelaire, Poems Selected and Arranged by Georges Guy; Period Records (Box 35)
    - An Anthology of French Poetry Volume One: From Charles D'Orleans to Tristan L'Hermite, Poems Selected and Arranged by Georges Guy; Period Records (Box 35)
    - Understanding and Appreciation of Poetry, Prepared by Morris Schreiber; Folkways Records (Box 35)
    - Metaphysical and Love Lyrics of the Seventeenth Century, a Reading by Sir Cedric Hardwicke and Robert Newton Directed by Howard O. Sackler; Caedmon Records (Box 35)
    - Bonzo Goes to Washington: 5 Minutes; Sleeping Bag Records (Box 35)
    - Just Another Asshole #5, edited by Barbara Ess and Glenn Branca; JAA (Box 35)
    - Liverpool Scene: Bread on the Night; RCA Records (Box 35)
    - Jill Kroesen, Stop Vicious Cycles; Lovely Music (Box 35)
    - Laurie Anderson, Big Science; Warner Bros. Records (Box 35)
    - Laurie Anderson: O Superman/ Walk the Dog; Warner Bros. Records (Box 35)
    - Bonzo Dog Doo/Dah Band, Gorilla; Imperial Records (Box 36)
    - Bonzo Dog Band, Let's Make Up and be Friendly; United Artists Records (Box 36)
    - Laurie Anderson, Mister Heartbreak; Waner Bros. Records (Box 36)
    - State of the Union; Zoar Records (Box 36)
    - State of the Union; Zoar Records (Box 36)
    - The Jim Carroll Band, Dry Dreams; ATCO Records (Box 36)
    - Falco, Rock Me Amadeus, the American Edit; A and M Records (Box 36)
    - Duck's Breath Mystery Theatre, Born to be Tiled; Rounder Records (Box 36)
    - Roger Ruskin Spear, Electric Shocks; United Artists Records (Box 36)
    - Bongos Bass and Bob; [Penn Jillette] (Box 36)
    - Karen Finley, Tales of Taboo; Pow Wow Art International (Box 36)
    - Songs of Leonard Cohen; CBS Records (Box 36)
    - Leonard Cohen, Songs From a Room; CBS Records (Box 36)
    - Medieval Romance Poetry, A Survey of Medieval Romance Literatures by Dr. Mario Pei; Folkways Records (Box 36)
    - United States Presidents' Series, Actual Speeches of Franklin D. Roosevelt and John F. Kennedy; Library in Sound Records (Box 36)
    - Marilyn Monroe, The Complete Recordings; Recording Arts Reference Edition (Box 36)
    - Bob Rosenthal, Poetry Project Test Pressings; RGH Record Manufacturing Corp. [Two LPs] (Box 36)
    - Poetry Olympics Volume 1; All Round Records (Box 36)
    - Terry Garthwaite, Bobbie Louise Hawkins, Rosalie Sorrels, Live at the Great American Music Hall; Flying Fish Records (Box 36)
    - The World Record, Readings at the St. Mark's Poetry Project 1969-1980; The Poetry Project (Box 36)
    - Morrison St., A Spoken Word Anthology; Paris Records (Box 36)
    - Meredith Monk/Dolmen Music; ECM Records (Box 36)
    - Ben Bagley Presents Kenward Elmslie in Palais Bimbo Lounge Show; Painted Smiles Records (Box 36)
    - Mao Tse-Tung: Quotations From the Chairman Read by Martin Donegan; Peerless Records (Box 36)
    - Chile: Songs for the Resistance; Paredon Records (Box 36)
    - We Shall Overcome, Songs of the "Freedom Riders" and the "Sit-Ins;" Folkway Records (Box 36)
    - Test Pressing, Version 1, Volume 1; Tartown Record Co. (Box 36)
    - Roxanne Shante Def Mix Volume 1; Pop Art Records (Box 36)
    - RZA Presents Wu-Tang Killa Bees, The Swarm Volume 1; Wu-Tang Records, Inc. (Box 36)
    - He's the D.J., I'm the Rapper, D.J. Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince; Jive Records (Box 36)
    - Roxanne Shante, Roxanne's Revenge; Pop Art Records (Box 36)
    - Run-D.M.C.; Profile Records, Inc. (Box 36)
    - Newcleus, Jam on It; Sunnyview Records, Inc. (Box 37)
    - Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew; Reality Records (Box 37)
    - Beastie Boys: Cooky Puss, Bonus Batter, Beastie Revolution; Ratcage Mir (Box 37)
    - Kurtis Blow: Tough; Mercury (Box 37)
    - Just Ice; Fresh Records (Box 37)
    - Grandmixer DST Crazy Cuts; Island Records, Inc. (Box 37)
    - L.L. Cool J, Radio; Def Jam Recordings (Box 37)
    - Sutra Single, Disco 3; Sutra Records, Inc. (Box 37)
    - L.L. Cool J, I Need a Beat/You'll Rock (Remix); Def Jam Recordings (Box 37)
    - Martin Luther, Hurt 'Em Bad and the S.C. Band; Profile Records, Inc. (Box 37)
    - D.J. Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince Rock the House; Jive (Box 37)
    - Count Coolout, Rhythm Rap Rock; WMOT Records (Box 37)
    - Beastie Boys, Licensed to Ill; Def Jam Recordings (Box 37)
    - Ice Cube, AmeriKKKa's Most Wanted; Priority Records (Box 37)
    - Krush Groove, Music from the Original Motion Picture Sound Track; Warner Bros. Records (Box 37)
    - Wild Style; Animal Records (Box 37)
    - That's the Joint, Funky 4+1; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - That's the Joint, Vocal, Funky 4 Plus 1; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - That's the Joint, Vocal, Funky 4 Plus 1; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - Freedom, Grandmaster Flash and the Furious 5; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - Kurtis Blow, "The Breaks;" Mercury (Box 37)
    - Ed Sanders, Beer Cans on the Moon; Reprise Records (Box 37)
    - The Fugs, Star Peace; New Rose Records (Box 37)
    - The Fugs, It Crawled Into My Hand, Honest; Reprise Records (Box 37)
    - The Fugs, It Crawled Into My Hand, Honest; Reprise Records (Box 37)
    - Fantasy, Doug E. Fresh and the Get Fresh Crew; Reality Records (Box 37)
    - Grand Master Flash and Furious Five, It's Nasty (Genius of Love); Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - Sugarhill Gang, Rapper's Delight; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - Sugarhill Gang, Rapper's Delight; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - Grand Master Flash and the Furious Five Featuring Melle Mel and Duke Bootee, The Message; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - The Adventures of Grandmaster Flash on the Wheels of Steel/Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, The Party Mix; Sugar Hill Records (Box 37)
    - Through the Eyes of Terry Ber, Songs of Terry Ber and Other Poets; World Pacific, a Division of Liberty Records, Inc. (Box 37)
    - Poet Song, Tina and David Meltzer; Vanguard (Box 37)
    - The Best of Mimi and Richard Farina; Vanguard (Box 37)
    - D.J. Wally and Edwin Torres, Rhumba Bomballet/Embroidered Delirium; Kill Rock Stars (Box 37)
    - D.J. Wally and Edwin Torres, Rhumba Bomballet/Embroidered Delirium; Kill Rock Stars (Box 37)
    - The 1969 Warner/Reprise Songbook; Warner Bros. Records, Inc. (Box 37)
    - The Fugs First Album; Base Record (Box 37)
    - The Fugs First Album, Reissue of Broadside BR 304; ESP Disk (Box 37)
    - The Fugs. No More Slavery; New Rose Records (Box 37)
    - The Fugs, 1028; Base Record (Box 37)
    - The Fugs, 1028; ESP Disk (Box 37)
    - Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, Doc at the Radar Station; Virgin Records, Ltd. (DEACCESSIONED AUGUST 2010) (Box 38)
    - Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, Unconditionally Guaranteed; Virdin Records, Ltd. (Box 38)
    - Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, Trout Mask Replica; Straight Records (Box 38)
    - Reflections and Poetry; Silhouette Music (Box 38)
    - Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, Ice Cream for Crow; Virgin Records, Ltd. (DEACCESSIONED AUGUST 2010) (Box 38)
    - Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, Clear Spot; Reprise Records (Box 38)
    - Zapped, Bizarre; Reprise Records (Box 38)
    - Zapped, Bizarre; Reprise Records (Box 38)
    - Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, Grow Fins Volume II: Trout Mask House Sessions 1969; Xeric (Box 38)
    - Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, Shiny Beast (Bat Chain Puller); Virgin Records, Ltd. (DEACCESSIONED AUGUST 2010) (Box 38)
    - Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, Bluejeans and Moonbeams; Virgin Records, Ltd. (Box 38)
    - Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band, Safe as Milk; Buddha Records (Box 38)
  - Subseries B: Vinyl Recordings - EPs, 7 in.
    - Laurie Anderson, O Superman/Walk the Dog; Warner Bros. Records, Inc. (Box 39)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 7 in.
    - Wordcore Volume One: Kathleen Hanna, Rockstar/Slim Moon, Mean; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, [33 1/3] rpm; 7 in.
    - Wordcore Volume One: Kathleen Hanna, Rockstar/Slim Moon, Mean; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume One: Kathleen Hanna, Rockstar/Slim Moon, Mean; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Two: Stacey Levine, Sweethearts Girl /Peter Toliver, Wad Load Boy; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Two: Stacey Levine, Sweethearts Girl /Peter Toliver, Wad Load Boy; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Three: Jean Smith, Carboni Angel; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Three: Jean Smith, Carboni Angel; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Four: Penny Arcade, A Cunt is a Useful Thing!; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Four: Penny Arcade, A Cunt is a Useful Thing!; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Five: She's Good People; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Five: She's Good People; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Six: Peter Plate, History Comes Around Like Snipers on a Rooftop; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Six: Peter Plate, History Comes Around Like Snipers on a Rooftop; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Seven: Exene Cervenka; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Seven: Exene Cervenka; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - KRS Wordcore Volume Eight: Emily KYZ, Jimmy Page Loves Lori Maddox, Sinatra Walks Out; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - KRS Wordcore Volume Eight: Emily KYZ, Jimmy Page Loves Lori Maddox, Sinatra Walks Out; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Nine: Nicole Panter, The Story Lady; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - Wordcore Volume Ten: Billy Chikdish, Hangman Comunication; Kill Rock Stars (Box 39)
    - The Pendulum Floors; Villa Villakula Records (Box 39)
    - Word and Sound with Instruments, Featuring Edwin Torres, Pavel Fajt, Wallace Stevens, KLMR; 715 Records (Box 39)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, 45 rpm; 7 in.
    - Jennifer Blowdryer, My Parents Were Beatniks/I Have a Nightclub Pig Inside of Me; 715 Records (Box 39)
    - KLMR-Mali, Edwin Torres-"Mirror-Fuc-Cation, "Wallace Stevens-Bantoms in Pine Woods,Torres-Knoll, E-Loop/Pavel Fajt-1995 Hermit Drum Solo; 715 Records (Box 39)
    - Allen Ginsberg with the Gluons, Birdbrain; Alekos Records (Box 39)
    - Anne Waldman, Uh-Oh Plutonium!; Hyacinth Girls Music (Box 39)
    - Panic DJ's Rock 'n' Roll Mythology/Made in Japan; Words on 45 (Box 39)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, [45] rpm; 7 in.
    - Panic DJ's Rock 'n' Roll Mythology/Made in Japan; Words on 45 (Box 39)
      Format: Sound Disc: Analog, [45] rpm; 7 in. The sleeve does not match the disc's label.
    - Bingo Gazingo and the Eigth Grade, "Are You a Lover?" b/w "Juice with Juice;" Holy Plastic (Box 39)
    - Un Cuerpo Exquisito, Te Quiere, Tu Amante Bilinque; Villa Villakula Records (Box 39)
    - Buford Hicks Band, ZZ Queen/Pickup Truck; Prairie Dust Records (Box 39)
    - Lulu Revue, A.W.O.L./ My Place Assassin, Iceland; Zanon Records (Box 39)
    - The Newshounds, The Press Conference; Ragun Records (Box 39)
    - Private Angst; Catheart Records (Box 39)
    - Bazingo Gazingo Loves You So Fucking Much He Can't Shit; Metaphysical Dumping Grounds Records (Box 39)
    - The Stimulators, Loud Fast Rules!/Run Run Run; The Stimulators (Box 39)
    - Didus and the Fabulous Mascarenes, So and So/These Boots Are Made for Walkin'; Xtinct Records (Box 39)
    - Santo, Son of A Working Man/Loisaida; The Source Unltd Records and Tapes (Box 39)
    - Beanie the Singing Dog with the Beanettes, Beanie for Peace; Conscious Decision Records (Box 39)
    - Re-Flex, The Politics of Dancing/Flex It!; Capitol Records (Box 39)
    - The Mighty Imperials, Kick the Bucket/Toothpick; Desco Records (Box 39)
    - Miguel Algarin-"She," Edwin Torres-"equinnical kiss," Sean G. Meehan-"drumset"; Trust (Box 39)
    - Emily XYZ, Who Shot Sadat/The Stripsearch, Hey Kid; InylRepellant (Box 39)
    - Jill Kroesen, I Really Want to Bomb You, Jesus Song; Infidelity (Box 39)
    - The Revolution of Everyday Life, Dos with Denis Mahoney/Black Pig Liberation Front; Pop Rocket Records (Box 39)
    - Doomed #001: Money, Material Takeover/White Lies, Desensitized; Doomed Recordz (Box 39)
    - Knowbody, Love Makes You Vicious; R and R Produtions (Box 39)
    - Essential Logic, Popcorn Boy, Waddle You Do?, Flora Force; Rough Trade and Logic Records (Box 39)
  - Subseries C: Vinyl Recordings - African American
    Items in this subseries reflect original order of Bob Holman.
    - The Last Poets Original from the Hit Movie "Right On!;" Juggernaut Records (Box 40)
    - Sidney Poitier Reads Poetry of the Black Man with Doris Belack, Music by the Brooks Male Chorus; United Artists Records (Box 40)
    - Sidney Poitier Reads Poetry of the Black Man with Doris Belack, Music by the Brooks Male Chorus; United Artists Records (Box 40)
    - Matzoh Balls, Slim and Slam; Caete Records (Box 40)
    - Adventures in Negro History Volume II: The Frederick Douglas Years 1817-1895; Highlight radio Productions (Box 40)
    - Beyond the Blues, American Negro Poetry: Brock Peters, Vinette Carroll, Cleo Laine, and Gordon Heath; Argo (Box 40)
    - Get Your Ass in the Water and Swim Like Me, Narrative Poetry from the Black Oral Tradition; Rounder Records (Box 40)
    - The Poetry of Langston Hughes Read by Ruby Dee and Ossie Davis; Caedmon Records, Ltd. (Box 40)
    - The Last Poets, Oh My People; Celluloid (Box 40)
    - The Last Poets, Time Has Come Sampler; Mercury Records (Box 40)
    - The Last Poets, Time Has Come Sampler; Mercury Records (Box 40)
    - Excerpts from Mouth Almighty's "Flippin' the Script, Rap Meets Poetry;" Mercury Records (Box 40)
    - Roy Hill Reads Poetry From Two Worlds, Recorded Live at Kansas State University, Washburn University, University of Kansas; Audio House (Box 40)
    - Amiri Baraka, Leroi Jones, New Music-New Poetry with David Murray and Steve McCall; India Navigation (Box 40)
    - Jayne Cortez and the Fire-Spitters, There It Is; Bola Press (Box 40)
    - Nicolas Guillen, Poet Laureate of Revolutionary Cuba; Folkways Records (Box 40)
    - Jose Coronel Urtecho, Poesia, Palabra de Esta America; Casa de las Americas (Box 40)
    - Jayne Cortez, Unsbmissive Blues; Bola Press (Box 40)
    - Loose Joints, Poetry by Pedro Pietri; Folkways Records (Box 40)
    - Ornette Coleman, Science Fiction; Columbia Records (Box 40)
    - Imamu Amiri Baraka (Le Roi Jones), The Original Last Poets, Black Spirits: Festival of New Black Poets in America; Black Forum (Box 40)
    - LKJ in Dub; Mango Records (Box 40)
    - Linton Kwesi Johnson, Bass Culture; Mango Records (Box 40)
    - Linton Kwesi Johnson, Dread Beat an' Blood; Virgin Records (Box 40)
    - Linton Kwesi Johnson, Making History; Mango Records (Box 40)
    - Linton Kwesi Johnson, Reggae Reggae Great Greats; Mango Records (Box 40)
    - Linton Kwesi Johnson, Forces of Victory; Mango Records (Box 40)
    - Lillian Allen, Revolutionary Tea Party; Redwood Records (Box 40)
    - Lillian Allen, Conditions Critical; Redwood Records (Box 40)
    - Word Soun' 'Ave Power Reggae Poetry; Heartbeat (Box 40)
    - Woman Talk, Caribbean Dub Poetry; Heartbeat (Box 40)
    - Akabu; Viva Records (Box 40)
    - Michael Smith, "Mi C-YaaN beLieVe iT;" Mango Records (Box 40)
    - Clifton Joseph with the Livestock Band, Oral/Trans/Missions; Verse to Vinyl Records (Box 40)
    - Conjure: Music for the Texts of Ishmael Reed; American Clave (Box 40)
    - The Last Poets, Douglas 3; Douglas Communications (Box 40)
  - Subseries D: Vinyl Recordings - Various Poets
    - Lord Buckley, A Most Immaculately Hip Aritocrat; Straight Records (Box 41)
    - Lord Buckley in Concert; Demon Verbals (Box 41)
    - Lord Buckley, Bad Rapping of the Marquis de Sade in Newly Discovered Live Performances; World Pacific (Box 41)
    - The Sick Humor of Lenny Bruce; Fantasy (Box 41)